(Howard:)All right, that's the last servo.
(Howard:)Behold the Mobile Omnidirectional
Neutralization and Termination Eradicator.
(Howard:)Or...
ALL:
Monte.
(Howard:)Featuring one articulated
razor-sharp killing saw...
...one polycarbonate grinding wheel...
...steel-armor plate exoskeleton
top and bottom.
(Howard:)Enough horsepower to drive
110 pounds of mechanized death...
(Howard:)...from zero to holy crap in 4.8 seconds.
(Sheldon:)Is it wrong to say I love our killer robot?
(Raj:)As with my father,
I both love and fear it.
(Howard:)All right, enough chitchat.
Let's destroy something.
ALL:
One, two, three. Unh.
RAJESH: Okay, what shall be first
to taste the wrath of Monte?
(Leonard:)Maybe we should start small.
RAJESH: Okay. Oh, perhaps today
is the day we finally find out...
...what's inside the Magic 8 Ball.
Did it when I was 4.
It's an icosahedral die
floating in tinted blue water.
(Raj:)Man, call spoiler alert
before you say things like that.